SITI HAWA TUMIRAN

FINANCE, ADMIN, CUSTOMER SUPPORT AND PROJECT ASSISTANCE

CONTACT

16 B, KG. SG. JAGONG, SG. LAYAR, 08000 SG. PETANI, KEDAH DARUL AMAN.

6014 - 669 0701

shawatumiran@gmail.com

Expected Salary: RM2000

SKILLS

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Microsoft Off.	9999
SPSS & MYOB	0000
Data handling	0000

PERSONAL SKILLS

Team Player	9999
Problem Solve	•••
Hardworking	••••
Work Etique	0000
Creative	0000

REFERENCES

MDM JAMIAH MOHAMAD

Assistance Manager, Maybank Bukit Indah Service Centre. 019-797 4699

MDM LAI HWE LIE (EVE)

Manager, APR Dept. OCBC Bank (M) Bhd 6010 – 220 3515



PROFILE

I am a project assistance with over two years professional working experience in a well known company. 26 years old, hardworking, and independent despite quickly adapt in new environment. Efficient when working as a team member and equipped with sufficient technique and skills to help your organization to achieve goals and ambitions.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

MALAYAN BANK BHD Sale Executive

Nov 2016 until May2017 (6 Months Contract)

- Exposed and sell Maybank products to target customer.
- Support in Administration
- > Attend to customer needs and request.

OCBC BANK (M) BHD Assistance Manager

Nov 2014 until April 2016 (1 ½ Years Contract)

- > Support, advice and handle related problem that faced by customers related with banking new system platform.
- Coordinate communication and deals with all related parties such as product owner, IT specialist, counterpart and branch representative to solve upcoming problem and satisfy customers needs while liaise with compliance to avoid breach
- Manage filing, prepared and reconciled any related report

TWOJ INTERNATIONAL (M) SDN BHD

Finance and Administrative Assistance

Feb 2014 until July 2014 (6 Month Contract)

- Prepared complete tender proposal document, assist in daily adhoc task and prepared invoice.
- Recorded all daily financial transaction in and out in MYOB Accounting system, reconciled financial report and statement.
- > Assist in documenting and filing all receipt and handling petty cash.

EDUCATIONS

NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF MALAYSIA (UKM)

Bachelor (Hons) in Business Management (Majoring Finance)

CGPA: 3.35/4.00

PERAK MATRICULATION COLLEGE

Certificate of Accounting

CGPA: 3.95/4.00

SMK TAN SRI OSMAN MD SAAT

Siiil Pelaiaran Malavsia

Result: 2A+, 1A, 1A-, 4B

> LANGGUAGE	ENGLISH	BAHASA
WRITTEN	••••	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$
SPOKEN	••••	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$